All right, I'll go ahead and start with the first one.
حسنًا، سأواصل وأبدأ من الخيار الأول.
It looks good, but it doesn't have the slash inside the closing tag, so
يبدو جيدًا، ولكن لا يتضمن شرطة مائلة داخل علامة الإغلاق، لذا
that one is incorrect.
فهذا الخيار غير صحيح.
Next up, there is an element nested inside a p element.
الخيار التالي، يوجد عنصر em بجوار العنصر p.
Now you haven't seen before, stands for emphasis, which just makes text italic.
ولم يسبق أن رأيتم العنصر em، يرمز إلى التوكيد، الذي يجعل النص مائلاً فحسب.
As it turns out there's actually nothing wrong with this except for the typo.
وكما يتضح، لا يوجد في الواقع شيء خاطئ في هذا الخيار سوى الخطأ الإملائي.
However, typos don't count as incorrectly formatted HTML, so
ومع ذلك، لا يُعد الخطأ الإملائي HTML منسَّق بطريقة غير صحيحة،
this one's actually good.
لذا فهذا خيار جيد فعلاً.
Then comes the third one, now notice that it's all green and looks weird.
بعد ذلك يأتي الخيار الثالث، لاحظوا الآن أنه مكتوب باللون الأخضر كاملاً ويبدو غريبًا.
This is a very good indication that this one is wrong.
وهذه إشارة جيدة للغاية على أن هذا الخيار خطأ.
I didn't include the greater than sign here inside the opening tag,
ولم أقم بتضمين علامة "أكبر من" هنا داخل العلامة الافتتاحية،
which made this whole thing a mess.
مما جعل الأمر كله فوضويًا.
Now one of the nice things about code editors is that they will
والآن يتمثل أحد الأشياء الجيدة بشأن محررات التعليمات البرمجية في أنها
change the formatting depending on whether or not the syntax is right.
ستغير التنسيق اعتمادًا على ما إذا كان بناء الجملة صحيحًا أم لا.
So because the syntax here is wrong, this is not valid HTML,
لذلك فإن HTML غير صالح لأن بناء الجملة هنا خطأ،
this all looks weird in green and
ويبدو ذلك كله غريبًا باللون الأخضر
it should be pretty obvious that something needs to get fixed.
ومن الواضح تمامًا أن هناك شيء ما يجب إصلاحه.
The last one looks really similar to the second.
يبدو الخيار الأخير شبيهًا حقًا بالخيار الثاني.
But there's a key difference.
ولكن هناك اختلاف أساسي.
I switched the closing tags here.
وهو أنني بدلت علامات الإغلاق هنا.
Now notice that the tag is being closed outside of the p tag and
لاحظوا الآن أن العلامة مغلقة خارج علامة p
the p tag's being closed inside the tag.
وأن علامة p مغلقة داخل علامة em.
That is wrong, this is a mess.
وذلك خطأ، فهذه فوضى.
The element is the child of the p element, and as such, you have to
حيث إن عنصر em فرع من العنصر p، وفي هذه الحالة، يجب
open it and then close it inside the p, like what's done right here.
فتحه وإغلاقه داخل p، كما تم فعله هنا بشكل صحيح.